J. Kabil

Thoothukudi, TAMIL NADU, IN 628251 jkabilstfcp_npy@indeedemail.com +91-9789283903

Mechanical Supervisor are responsible for keeping a variety of Machine, appliance and mechanical systems operating safety and efficiently. 5 years working experience in safety / pump, compressors, nozzle, steam boiler record of successfully using tools and maintain machinery and mechanical equipment. The repair and maintenance of pressure Vessels, pump, valve, pipe fitting, expert at troubleshooting mechanical, hydraulic and pneumatic systems.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 1992-01-29 Eligible to work in: India

Highest Career Level: 5+ years experience

Industry: Business Operations, Community & Social Service, Mathematics, Mechanical Engineering,

Mining & Oil, Oil & Gas, Energy, Power, Infrastructure, Water Treatment, Waste Management

Total years of experience: 9

Work Experience

Lecturer in Mechanical Department

St Xavier's polytechnic college - Seydunganallur, Tamil Nadu June 2020 to February 2023

Mechanical lecturer

Xavier polytechnic college seyunganallur - India February 2020 to February 2023

Teaching for the student

Mechanical supervisor

Tamilnadu Thermal Power Plant - Tuticorin, Tamil Nadu April 2016 to April 2016

Education

B.E (Mech) in Mechanical Activities

Anna University

kings engineering college - Nazareth, Tamil Nadu 2011

S.S.L.C in Tamil medium

Pope memorial hr sec school - Tuticorin, Tamil Nadu May 2003 to May 2008

Skills / IT Skills

- Organisational skills (8 years)
- · Microsoft Office
- Communication skills (1 year)
- Higher education teaching (2 years)
- Computer Knowledge: AUTO CAD, DCA Mechanical Activities: Antifreeze, LEL, H2 S Battery Replacement, Parts Washing, Oil Changes, Rags, Refrigerants, Engine Operations, Zinc Replacement, Commissioning Engineers. Systems: Steady Flow sty stem, Expansion of gases, Equilibrium of a Systems, Cooling Systems, Thermodynamic System, Valve Actuating Mechanism, Gas Turbine, Filtering Element, Super Charger Systems, Thermodynamic Cycle, Pump feed Systems, Gravity feed Systems, Open and Closed loop System.
- Food preparation
- Cash handling (4 years)
- Maintenance (5 years)
- Stocking (1 year)